<table width='100%'>
  <tr>
    <td valign='top'>
      <div>
        The SEARCH page is where your personalize the communication for your audience. It lets you search through the Office Live Small Business apps and lists that you have acces to and select those fields that you want to include in the communication.
        So if you want to personalize the communication to be some thing like "Dear Mr. John Smith, Your order number 2387 has been processed and shipped..." you'd want to include the fields "FirstName", "LastName" and "OrderNumber" in the message. The 
        SEARCH page applies to all supported communication channels: email, SMS and voice.
        
        <br/><br/>So let's see how this is done.
        <br/><br/><strong>NAVIGATE LISTS</strong><br/>        
        
        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Application Type</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is a list of the different types of Office Live Small Business Applications. Select the type of Application that you want to work with.
        </div>
        
        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Application</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is a list of applications that match the selected Application Type. Select the Application that you want to search through.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>List</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is a list of all the lists in the selected Application. Select the list in the application that has the fields (like FirstName, LastName, OrderNumber, etc.) that 
          you'd like to use for personalization.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>View</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is a list of all the views for the selected list. Select the view that you want to work with.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Linked List</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is a list of lookup lists used by the selected list. Select a linked list if you want to use any of the fields in it for personalization.
        </div>
        <br/><strong>Note: </strong>The Navigate Lists controls are enabled only when creating a new FYI. When you open an existing FYI, Navigate Lists are grayed out
        and cannot be changed.
        
        <br/><br/><strong>SELECT MESSAGE FIELDS</strong><br/>
        This shows the fields in the selected list. Use the "Yes" checkboxes to select the fields that you want to include in your message. 
        If a field is grayed out, it means that it uses a lookup list with that name.
        <br/><br/><strong>RULES</strong><br/>
        A rule is a criteria for searching for items in a list. An example of a rule would be "Order value greater than $100" or "ZIP code equals 96762". 
        A rule will filter out the search results and return only those that we're interested in. 
        <br/><br/>You can specify upto 2 rules. The rules can be chained with "AND" or "OR" conditions. This means that we can chain 2 rules to be either:
        <br/>"Order value greater than $100" <u>AND</u> "ZIP code equals 96762" or
        <br/>"Order value greater than $100" <u>OR</u> "ZIP code equals 96762"
        <br/><br/>A rule is made up of 4 parts:
        <br/>
      <br/>
      <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
        <i>
          <strong>Checkbox</strong>
        </i>
        <br/>Check this box if you want to include the rule.
      </div>
        <br/>
        
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Field</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is a list of fields for the selected list or view. The rule is applied on this field.
        </div>
        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Rule</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is the list of rules that can be applied to the Field. The types of rules that can be applied depends on the Field.
        </div>
        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Rule Value</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is the value that you specify for the rule.
        </div>
        
        <br/><br/><strong>CHECK QUERY</strong><br/>
        Click "Check Query" button to test your search. Upto 50 rows of results will be displayed values of the fields that you selected.

        <br/><br/><strong>SKIP SEARCH</strong><br/>
        If you do not want to include any personalization fields in your message, check the "Skip Search" checkbox. This will gray out all the other
        fields and controls on the SEARCH page.

        <br/><br/><strong>NEXT BUTTON</strong><br/>
        Clicking the "Next" button will take you to the "SELECT" page.
      </div>
    </td>
    <td valign='top'>
      <span style='margin-left:5px'>
        <img src='./images/page-description-help-icon.jpg' />
      </span>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>