<table width='100%'>
  <tr>
    <td valign='top'>
      <div>
        The MANAGE CONTACT LIST page is where your can manage your lists and contacts. You can add new items to your lists, edit exisiting items ans also delete list items.

        <br/><br/>So let's see how this is done.
        <br/><br/><strong>NAVIGATE LISTS</strong><br/>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Application Type</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is a list of the different types of Office Live Small Business Applications. Select the type of Application that you want to work with.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Application</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is a list of applications that match the selected Application Type. Select the Application that you want to search through.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>List</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is a list of all the lists in the selected Application. Select the list that you want to manage.          
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>View Data Button</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>Click this button to view the data in the selected list.
        </div>

        <br/>        

        <br/><br/><strong>LIST DATA</strong><br/>
        This shows the all the rows in the selected list.  
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
        <i>
          <strong>Edit Link</strong>
        </i>
        <br/>Click the Edit link against the row that you want to edit. You can change the values in the fields of the row. When done editing, click the "Update" link.
        To ignore changes made, click the "Cancel" link.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Upload File Link</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>To add new data to the list, click the "Upload File" link. Browse to the location of a comma-separated-file (CSV) that contains the new rows of data that you want
          to add to the list. After selecting the file, click the "Upload File" button.
          
          <br/><br/>NOTE: A comma-separated-file (CSV) is a text file that contains the values for rows of data that you want to upload to a list.
          For example, if you have a contact list that has First Name, Last Name and Email as its fields, create a CSV file that looks like this:<br/><br/>
          
          John,Doe,jd@hotmail.com<br/>
          Mary,Poppins,marypoppins@gmail.com<br></br>
          
          Each field is separated by a comma. Commas are not allowed to be a part of the field value itself.
                    
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Delete Rows Link</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>To delete one or more rows of data, select the check box against each row that you want to delete. Then click the "Delete" button.          
        </div>
      </div>
    </td>
    <td valign='top'>
      <span style='margin-left:5px'>
        <img src='./images/page-description-help-icon.jpg' />
      </span>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>