<table width='100%'>
  <tr>
    <td valign='top'>
      <div>
        This is the editor used to design the content and the look and feel of your email. 
        <br/><br/><strong>TEMPLATE EDITOR</strong>
        <br/>The Template Editor lets you create HTML-based emails using building blocks called "Templates". An email has 3 parts:        

        <br/><br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Subject Line: </strong>
          </i>
          Enter the subject of the email.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Message: </strong>
          </i>
          The message has 3 parts: Header, Body, Side Column. Click <a href='http://www.simplyfyi.com'>here</a> to learn more about the EMAIL EDITOR.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Signature: </strong>
          </i>
          The signature ("from") for the email.
        </div>

        <br/><br/><strong>TEXT EDITOR</strong>
        <br/>The Text Editor lets you create text-based emails using building blocks called "Templates". simplyfyi sends text-based
        emails as a back up for HTML-based emails to ensure that the text-email gets delivered if HTML-email gets blocked by the receiving 
        party's some email servers (done so usually for security reasons). A text email has 3 parts:

        <br/><br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Subject Line: </strong>
          </i>
          Enter the subject of the email.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Message: </strong>
          </i>
          The message has 3 parts: Header, Body, Side Column. Click <a href='http://www.simplyfyi.com'>here</a> to learn more about the EMAIL EDITOR..
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Signature: </strong>
          </i>
          The signature ("from") for the email.
        </div>

        <br/><br/><strong>EDITOR AND PREVIEW MODES</strong>
        <br/>After creating the structure and content of the email, you can switch to PREVIEW MODE by clicking the link at the top right.
        The PREVIEW MODE will display the email as the receipient would see it. It will also let you preview with the real data embedded.
        The THEME drop-down list in the PREVIEW mode lets you change the display and color theme of the email so that you can pick the
        theme of your choice.

        PREVIEW MODEs are available for both the TEMPLATE and TEXT EDITORS.
        <br/><br/>Click <a href='http://www.simplyfyi.com'>here</a> to learn more about the EMAIL EDITOR.
      </div>
    </td>
    <td valign='top'>
      <span style='margin-left:5px'>
        <img src='./images/page-description-help-icon.jpg' />
      </span>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>