<table width='100%'>
  <tr>
    <td valign='top'>
      <div>
        VOICE SHARE lets you schedule messages.
        <br/><br/>
        <strong>Save and run Loopback Test: </strong> Selecting his option and clicking SUBMIT saves the FYI and sends test VOICEs to yourself so that you can
        verify that everything looks good. Upto 5 VOICE messages will be sent. You will not be charged for sending test messages using this option.
        <br/><br/>
        <strong>Save and send now: </strong> Selecting this option and clicking SUBMIT saves the FYI and queues the messages for delivery NOW.
        <br/><br/>
        <strong>Save and schedule to send later: </strong> Selecting this option displays a date and time selector to schedule delivery in the future.
        Clicking SUBMIT saves the FYI and queues the messages for delivery at the designated date and time.
        <br/><br/>
        <strong>Send by value: </strong> Selecting this option displays a list of date fields in a list. A second list displays a range of time periods
        ( -15 mins, -30 mins, -1 day, -2 days, etc.). This is a list of "how much early before the value of the date in the selected date field in the first field" you want the message
        to be sent. Using this option, you can schedule messages to be delivered, say, "2 days before the appointment date".
        Clicking SUBMIT saves the FYI and queues the messages for delivery at the designated date and time.
        <br/><br/>
        <strong>Save but do not schedule as yet: </strong> Selecting this option and clicking SAVE saves the FYI but does not schedule it for delivery.
        This option is useful if you are working on a FYI over several days and do not want to schedule it for delivery till you are done.

        <br/><br/>
        <strong>Update changes: </strong> Selecting this option and clicking SAVE UPDATES saves the changes you made to the FYI. It does not affect the
        VOICE SHARE options that you set before. This is useful to change the contents of an existing FYI and saving the changes.
      </div>
    </td>
    <td valign='top'>
      <span style='margin-left:5px'>
        <img src='./images/page-description-help-icon.jpg' />
      </span>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>