<table width='100%'>
  <tr>
    <td valign='top'>
      <div>

        <strong>ACCOUNT INFO</strong>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'><i><strong>About You / About Your Organization</strong></i>
          <br/>This is the information about you and your organization. This information is used in the email footer information to identify to the receipient from whom the email was sent.          
        </div>
        <br/><br/><strong>OPTIONS</strong>
        <div style='padding-left:20px'>
          <i><strong>General settings</strong></i>
          <br/>Organization Logo Url: Enter the full URL of the logo of your website. <br/>Eg: http://www.mybiz.com/images/mybiz.jpg
        </div>
        <br/>
          <div style='padding-left:20px'>
            <i>
              <strong>Email Sender Identity Settings</strong>
            </i>
            <br/>This is the email address that your email receipients will see as the "From' address when they receive email from your business.
            The default Email Sender Indentity is fyi@simplyfyi.com. <br/><br/>To use your own Email Sender Identity (such as info@mybiz.com), please
          contact us at support@simplyfyi.com.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px'>
          <i>
            <strong>SMS Sender Identity Settings</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is the SMS phone number that your SMS receipients will see as the "From' number when they receive SMS messages from your business.
          The default SMS Sender Indentity is 916-409-6551. <br/><br/>To use your own SMS Sender Identity, please
          contact us at support@simplyfyi.com.
        </div>
        
        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px'>
          <i>
            <strong>Phone Sender Identity Settings</strong>
          </i>          
          <br/>This is the phone number that your voice message receipients will see as the caller identity when they receive voice messages from your business.
          The default Phone Sender Indentity is 916-409-6551. <br/><br/>To use your own Phone Sender Identity, please
          contact us at support@simplyfyi.com.
        </div>
        
        <br/><br/><strong>USAGE</strong>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>User</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is the name of the user associated with your Office Live Small Business account who scheduled the FYI.
        </div>
        <br/><div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Date</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is the date and time when the messages were queued for delivery.
        </div>
        <br/>        

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>+ or -</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>"+" means that simplyfyi UNITS are added to your account. You will see a "+" when (i) you buy simplyfyi UNITS or (ii) when you are awarded FREE units or (iii) when an adjustment is made.
          <br/><br/>"-" indicates that simplyfyi UNITS have been deducted from your account. You will see a "-" when messages are queued for delivery.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>FYI</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>A reference number for the transaction.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>EP</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>The type of end point (EP) - email, SMS or voice
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Qty</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>The number of messages sent in the batch.
        </div>
        
        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Units</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>This is the number of simplyfyi UNITS that have been added to or deducted from your account for this transaction.
        </div>

        <br/>
        <div style='padding-left:20px;'>
          <i>
            <strong>Balance</strong>
          </i>
          <br/>The running balance of simplyfyi UNITS in your account.
        </div>
                        
        <br />        
      </div>
    </td>
    <td valign='top'>
      <span style='margin-left:5px'>
        <img src='./images/page-description-help-icon.jpg' />
      </span>
    </td>
  </tr>
</table>